SEBASTIAN COLLISON

A versatile individual with strong roots in development and extensive knowledge of design software. With skillsets that range from graphic design within the Adobe Suite to VFX in Cinema4D, I am able to complete all design tasks set to a very high standard while still working hard in my free time to extend my current knowledge. Passionate to explore and build upon my skillsets, I am now devoted to perusing a career as a junior developer and am wanting to do so in the United Kingdom. I believe that with my previous experience and ability to approach problems with a wide range of tools and a deeper contextual understanding, I will be a great asset to the company.



RELOCATING

TO THE UK

CONTACT

EMAIL:

sebcollison@gmail.com

CALL:

+27 71 103 6659

ADDRESS:

30 Buitengracht Drive, Richwood, Cape Town, South Africa

WEBSITE:

www.sebcollison.com

SKILLS

Adobe Suite

- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- InDesign
- After Effects

Microsoft Office

- Word
- Excel
- Outlook
- Teams

Web Development

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript

3D Design

- Cinema4D
- Blender

HOBBIES

Art

earning.

Podcasts





WORK EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC DESIGN AND TECH ASSISTANT INTERNSHIP PLATFORM23 | 2021

- · Worked closely with the director and head of tech.
- Created CSVs and loaded new products to the website's store.
- · Responsible for making design changes to the website hosted on Shopify.
- Created 3D visualisations for a marble furniture collection consisting of 100+ pieces.
- Assisted with designing social media content and clothing graphics.

WAITRON

GREENS Restaurant | 2019 - Current

- Welcome and seat guests.
- Take orders and enter them into a POS system.
- Serve food and beverages.
- Prepare final bill and process payments.
- · Complete duties before and after shifts.

DJ AND SOUND MANAGEMENT

Live and Direct | 2014 - 2018

- Communicated with clients to meet their needs regarding music choice.
- Setup and managed both sound and lighting equipment during events.

EDUCATION HISTORY

2014 - 2018 Edgemead High School

National Senior Certificate

2021 Inscape Design College

Bachelor of Design

Completed 120 credits towards a BDes with 7 distinctions

2021 - Present FreeCodeCamp

Responsive Web Design

- Completed all lessons

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

- Completed 51 of 299 lessons

All completed certifications made avaliable upon request

REFERENCES

Tania de Vos

Director

tania@platform23.com

+27 82 407 110

Deidre April

Senior Manager

plattekloof@greensrestaurant.co.za +27 21 558 0855

+27 21 338 083